Guide to the J. Arthur (Jesse Arthur) Younger Papers, 1951-1968
Department of Special Collections
- Rizley, Ross (1892 -); Dist. judge (Box 6, Folder 18, Folder 21)
- Roads (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Roberts, Kenneth A. (1912 -); Cong. (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Roberts, Ralph (1905 -); Govt. official (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Robinson, Howard W. () (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A. (1908 -); Gov. of N.Y. (Box 15, Folder 5, Folder 6)
- Roderick, C. R. () (Box 9, Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 17)
- Rogers, Edith N. (1881 -); Cong., 5th Mass. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Rogers, Paul (1921 -); Cong., 6th Fla. (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Roland, E. J. () (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Romney, George (1907 -) (Box 15, Folder 10)
- ROOSEVELT, THEODORE (REFERENCE FILE) 1953 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Roudebush, Richard L. (1918 -); Cong., 6th Ind. (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Rousos, Ioannis (Private bill) (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Rowley, James R. (1908 -); Chief of U.S. Secret Service (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Ruby, Charles H. () (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Rutberg, A. A. () (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Sarnoff, Robert W. (1918 -); Broadcasting exec. (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Sadlak, Antoni N. () (Box 15, Folder 12)
- St. George, Katherine (); Cong., 28th N. Y. (Box 15, Folder 6, Folder 12)
- SAN BRUNO FEDERAL RECORDS CENTER (Box 18, Folder 8)
- SAN CARLOS AIRPORT (Box 18, Folder 9)
- San Filippo, Linda B. (Private bill) (Box 3, Folder 6)
- SAN FRANCISCO INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT
  - 1957 - 1958 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - 1959 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - 1960 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - 1961 - 1962 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - 1963 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- SAN FRANCISCO NAVAL SHIPYARD, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- SAN MATEO COUNTY (GENERAL)
  - 1964 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - 1966 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- SAN MATEO COUNTY STATISTICS (Box 18, Folder 18)
- SAN MATEO CREEK (Box 18, Folder 19)
- SAN MATEO FEDERAL BUILDING (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Saunel, D. S. () (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Saxon, James J. () (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Scammon, Richard M. (1915 -); Polit. scientist (Box 6, Folder 15, Box 15, Folder 5)
- Scherer, Gordon H. (1906 -); Cong., 1st Ohio (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Schottland, Charles I. (1906 -); College dean (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Schwengel, Fred (1907 -); Cong., 1st Iowa (Box 15, Folder 12)
- SCIENCE (GENERAL), 1963 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- SCIENCE & SPACE PROGRAM, 1964 - 1965 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Scott, Hugh (1900 -); Senator, Pa. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Scott, Walter K. (1915 -); Govt. official (Box 11, Folder 24, Box 20, Folder 4)
- Scrivner, Errett P. (1898 -); Cong., 2nd Kans. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Scudder, Hubert B. () (Box 6, Folder 8, Box 13, Folder 6)
- Seaborg, Glenn T. (1912 -); Univ. chancellor (Box 17, Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 14)
- SECURITIES & EXCHANGE COMM.
  - 1957 - 1964 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- SECURITY CHECKS, 1965 - 1966 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Sefert, J. B. () (Box 12, Folder 7)
- SELECTIVE SERVICE SYSTEM
  - 1955 - 1964 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - 1966(beginning June 1) (Box 18, Folder 26)
- SENATE, 1963 - 1965 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Sevier, Rudolph (1897 -); Steamship co. exec. (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Seward, Pere F. (1895 -); Govt. official (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Shafer. Raymond P. () (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Shaw, William D. () (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Shelley, John F. (1905 -); Cong., 5th Cal. (Box 6, Folder 6, Folder 15, Box 13, Box 16, Folder 1, Box 22, Folder 10)
- SHIPPING (GENERAL), 1963 - 1966 (Box 18, Folder 30)
- Shipbuilding (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Shipley, R. B. () (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Shipping (Cal.) (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Shriver, Robert Sargent Jr. (1915 -); Real estate mngmt. (Box 9, Folder 17, Box 11, Folder 5, Box 12, Folder 30, Box 14, Folder 13, Box 22, Folder 9)
- Siedle, E. George (1889 -); Asst postmaster gen. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- SIERRA (TRANS - SIERRA HIGHWAY) (Box 18, Folder 31)
- Sierra Club (Box 12, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 10)
- Sifuentes, Andrew (Private bill) (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Siler, Eugene (1900 -); Cong., 8th Ky. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Simon, Louis S. () (Box 4, Folder 1, Box 15, Folder 9)
- Simpson, Richard, (1900 -); Cong., 17th & 18th Pa. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Sinclair, Peter T. (1906 -); Pulp & paper exec. (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Siscoe, Frank G. (1913 -); Fgn. serv. officer (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Slusser, Charles E. (1892 -); Govt. official
- SMALL BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION
  - 1955 - 1957 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - 1965 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Misc. (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Smith, Donald W. (1906 -); Fgn. serv. officer (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Smith. H. Allen (1909 -); Cong., 20th Cal. (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Smith, Howard W. (1883 -); 8th Va. (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Snyder, Harold E. () (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Snyder, Murray (1911 -); Govt. official (Box 9, Folder 7)
- SOCIAL SECURITY
- SOCIALISM, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - 1965 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - 1966 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Sonic boom (Dept. of Air Force) (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Southwick, Paul () (Box 20, Folder 20)
- SPEAKERS, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- SPEECHES BY YOUNGER
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - 1964 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - 1965 - 1967 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Constitution (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Lincoln Day (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Others (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 8, Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 16, Folder 17)
- SPORTS
  - General, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Water Polo Team, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Spoto, Laninia (Private bill) (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Staats, Elmer B. (1914 -); Govt. official (Box 5, Folder 39, Box 18, Folder 13)
- Stahr, Elvis J. (1916 -); University president (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Stallings, E. Robert () (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Stalzer, William J. () (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Stanford Linear Accelerator (Box 17, Folder 7, Folder 8, Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 15)
- STANFORD UNIVERSITY (Box 12, Folder 29, Box 19, Folder 18)
- STANFORD VILLAGE, 1953 - 1958 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Stans, Maurice H. (1908 -); Govt. official (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Stanton, Frank (1908 -); Broadcasting exec. (Box 2, Folder 21, Box 4, Folder 1, Box 17, Folder 23)
- Starkey, J. H. () (Box 2, Folder 4)
- STATE DEPARTMENT
  - Burlingame HS. Orchestra (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Amelia Earhart story (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Cases, 1955 - 1956 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Cases, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Cases, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Cases, 1959 - 1960 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Cases, 1961 - 1962 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Ecuador trip (Box 20, Folder 6)
- STATE DEPARTMENT, GENERAL
  - 1955 - 1956(1) (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - 1955 - 1956(2) (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - 1957 - 1958 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - 1959 - 1960 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - 1961 - 1962 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Statehood, Hawaii (Box 3, Folder 34)
- STEEL PRICE INCREASE, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Stennis, John C. (1901 -); Senator, Miss. (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Sterling, J. E. Wallace (1906 -); Univ. pres. (Box 3, Folder 15, Box 12, Folder 29)
- Stiletto, Annie (Private bill) (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Stock distributions (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Stone, John F. (1909 -); Fgn. Serv. officer (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Stone, Ralph H. (1894 -); Govt. official (Box 21, Folder 9, Folder 10, Folder 12)
- Strauss, Lewis L. (1896 -); Govt. official (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Streibert, Theodore C. (1899 -); Radio exec. (Box 11, Folder 16, Box 21, Folder 1)
- Strubinger, D. B. () (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Subsidies, farm (Box 4, Folder 17)
- SUBVERSIVE ACTIVITIES CONTROL BOARD, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Summerfield, Arthur E. (1899 -); Postmaster gen., U.S.A. (Box 16, Folder 1, Folder 2)
- SUPREME COURT
  - 1963 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - 1965 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- SURPLUS GOVERNMENT PROPERTY
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - 1965 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Sutter, Johann, kin claims (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Sutton, W. J. () (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Swidler, Joseph C. (1907 -); Lawyer (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Swing, Joseph M. (1894 -); Govt. official (Box 3, Folder 8, Folder 24, Folder 27, Box 11, Folder 22, Box 5, Folder 2, Folder 21, Box 20, Folder 1, Folder 4)
- Switzer, Mary E. (1900 -); Govt. official (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Sylvester, Arthur (1901 -); Newspaperman (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Taber, John (1880 -); Cong., 36th & 38th N.Y. (Box 9, Folder 6, Box 17, Folder 30)
- Taft, William H. III (1915 -); Diplomat
- Talbot, Joseph E. (1901 -); Govt. official (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Talbot, Harold E. () (Box 19, Folder 20)
- TANFORAN PROPERTY (Box 13, Folder 32, Box 20, Folder 13)
- TAPES FOR DIST., 1959 - 1960 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- TARIFF, GENERAL
  - 1959 - 1960 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- TARIFFS, 1955 - 1956
  - Tariff Commission Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Tariff Commission Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Tariff Commission Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Tarver, Robert (Private bill) (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Taswell, H. L. T. () (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Tax (Federal Estate), Life insurance to cover (Box 4, Folder 14)
- TAXES, GENERAL, 1955 - 1966 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- TAXES, INCOME, 1963 - 1966 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Teague, Charles M. (1909 - 1973); Cong., 13th Cal. (Box 5, Folder 37, Box 9, Folder 33)
- Teague, Milton M. (1902 -); Business exec. (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Teague, Olin Earl (1910 -); Cong., 6th Tex. (Box 21, Folder 15)
- TENNESSEE VALLEY AUTHORITY, 1964 - 1966 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- THANK YOU LETTERS RECEIVED, 1959 - 1960 (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Thomas, Charles S. (1897 -); Sec. of Navy (Box 4, Folder 22, Box 9, Folder 6, Box 13, Folder 29, Folder 31, Box 17, Folder 28)
- Thomas, Sheldon () (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Thompson, Benjamin H. () (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Thompson, Ruth P. (1895 -); author (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Thomson, Keith, (1919 -); Cong., at large (Box 13, Folder 6, Box 15, Folder 12)
- Thornberry, William H. (1909 -); Cong., 10th Tex. (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Tieburg, Albert B. () (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Tindell, Arthur, claims (Private bill) (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Tinsley, Thomas A. () (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Tipton, Stuart G. (1910 -); Lawyer (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Tompkins, George W. () (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Tower, John G. (1925 -); Senator, Tex. (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Townsend, Dallas S. (1888 -); Lawyer (Box 12, Folder 18)
- TRADE (FEDERAL TRADE COMM.) (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Trade (Box 9, Folder 33, Folder 34)
- TRANSPORTATION (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Transportation and Communications, Dept. of (Proposal) (Box 4, Folder 27)
- TRAVEL, GENERAL (Box 20, Folder 27)
- TREASURY DEPARTMENT
  - 1955 - 1956 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - 1957 - 1958 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - 1959 - 1960 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - 1963 - 1966 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- TREATIES, GENERAL, 1963 - 1966 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Trowbridge, Alexander B. () (Box 20, Folder 20)
- TRUCKING (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Tucker, Raymond R. (1896 -); City official (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Tuohy, Walter J. (1901 -); Pres., Chesapeake & Ohio Railway Co. (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Turner, Allen R. () (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Udall, Stewart L. (1920 -); Cong., 2nd Ariz. (Box 5, Folder 39, Box 12, Folder 5, Box 22, Folder 16)
- Unemployment (Box 9, Folder 21)
- UNITED NATIONS (CORRESPONDENCE), 1955 - 1956 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- UNITED NATIONS (MISCELLANEOUS) 1959 - 1966 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- United Nations, admission of mainland China (Box 4, Folder 10, Box 15, Folder 35)
- UNITED STATES INFORMATION AGENCY, 1955 - 1966 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- UNIVERSITY VILLAGE (Box 21, Folder 2)
- UPPMAN, INGEGERD, 1964 - 1965 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- URBICULTURE (HR 1864)
  - 1954 - 1955 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - 1956 (Box 21, Folder 6, Folder 5)
  - 1957 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Urbiculture, Dept. of (proposal) (Box 4, Folder 25, Folder 26)
- URBICULTURE HEARING FILE (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Utt, James Boyd (1899 -); Cong., 28th Cal. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Valenti, Jack () (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Vandel, Heuvel A. () (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Van Pelt, William K. (1905 -); Cong. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Vass, Lawrence C. (1909 -); Govt. official (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Vaughn, Jack H. (1920 -); Govt. official (Box 14, Folder 13)
- VETERAN'S ADMINISTRATION
  - 1955 - 1956 (Box 21, Folder 9, Folder 11, Folder 10)
  - 1957 - 1958 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - 1956 - 1958 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - 1959 - 1960 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - 1961 - 1962 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - 1962 - 1966 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - General (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - V. A. Hospital in Palo Alto (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Vinson, Carl (1883 -); Cong., 6th & 10th Ga. (Box 3, Folder 22, Box 13, Folder 32)
- VISITORS
  - 1962 - 1964 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - 1966(to June 1) (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - 1966(beginning June) (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Vitamins (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Vorys, John M. () (Box 15, Folder 12)
- VOTING
  - General (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Records and surveys (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Younger (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Vursell, Charles W. () (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Waddell, Harold N. (1911 -); Fgn. serv. officer (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Wade, Leigh () (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Wade, Roy L. () (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Wailes, Edward T. (1903 -); Ambassador (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Wainright, Stuyvesant II (1921 -); Cong., 1st N.Y. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Wakelin, James H. Jr. (1911 -); Govt. official (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Walrath, Lawrence K. (1909 -); Govt. official (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Walsh, Lawrence E. (1912 -); U.S. Dep. Atty. Gen. (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Walter, Francis E. (1894 -); Cong., 15th Pa. (Box 3, Folder 27, Box 5, Folder 2, Folder 10, Folder 13)
- War claims (against Germany and Japan) (Box 3, Folder 19, Box 4, Folder 2)
- War on Poverty (Box 3, Folder 39, Box 4, Folder 18)
- Ward, Chester (1907 -); Naval officer (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Washington, George: Appt. as general of the armies (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Washington, D. C. (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Water (California) (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Water Resources
- Watson, James T. () (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Watson, Robert C. (1890 -); Lawyer (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Weaver, Philip H. (1919 -); Cong., 1st Neb. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Weaver, Robert Clifton (1907 -); Economist (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Webb, William H. (1896 -); Lawyer (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Webster, E. M. () (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Webster, Paul K. () (Box 4, Folder 14, Box 12, Folder 6)
- Weeks, Sinclair (1893 -); Sec. of Commerce (Box 7, Folder 16, Folder 18)
- Weinberger, Caspar W. () (Box 8, Folder 6, Box 14, Folder 28, Folder 31, Box 15, Folder 3, Box 17, Folder 21)
- Weitzel, Frank H. (1907 -); Govt. official (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Welch, Robert (1899 -); Govt. official (Box 19, Folder 20, Folder 22, Box 20, Folder 1, Folder 2)
- Wells, Preis V. () (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Weltner, Charles L. () (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Werts, Leo R. (1905 -); Govt. official (Box 2, Folder 2)
- West. Benjamin (1911 -); City official (Box 21, Folder 7)
- WEST, WALTER, 1963 - 1966 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- WATER RESOURCES
  - 1963 - 1964 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - 1965 - 1966 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- WAR CLAIMS
  - 1963 - 1966 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Anthony Janac, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- WAR ON POVERTY
  - 1965 - 1966(through May) (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - 1966(June - Dec.) (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Westland, Jack (1904 -); Cong., 2nd Wash. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- WEST POINT TRIPS (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Whalley, J. Irving (); Cong., 18th Pa. (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Wharton, James E. (1899 -); Cong., 29th N. Y. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- WHISKEYTOWN PROPERTY (Box 22, Folder 16)
- White, Ivan B. (1907 -); Fgn. serv. officer (Box 20, Folder 3)
- White, Lee C. () (Box 5, Folder 39, Box 17, Folder 14)
- White, Robert M. II (1915 -); Newspaperman (Box 14, Folder 5)
- WHITE HOUSE
  - 1955 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - 1959 - 1965 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Whitney, John H. (1904 -); Ambassador (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Whittier, Sumner G. (1911 -); Govt. official (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Whitton, Rex M. (1898 -); State official (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Whyte, William G. ()
- Wieland, William A. (1917 -); Fgn. serv. officer (Box 20, Folder 6)
- WILDLIFE CONSERVATION (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Williams, Walter (1894 -); Banking exec. (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Williams, William R. () (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Willis, Edwin E. (1904 -); Cong., 3rd La. (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Wilson, Earl (1907 -); Columnist, commentator (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Wilson, Henry H. Jr. (1921 -); Asst. to pres. (Box 7, Folder 34, Box 12, Folder 15)
- Wilson, Kenneth L. (1896 -); Athletic Comm. (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Wilson, Robert (1916 -); Cong., 30th Cal. (Box 3, Folder 10, Box 6, Folder 20, Box 15, Folder 8, Folder 9, Folder 12, Folder 21)
- Wirth, Conrad L. (1899 -); Govt. official (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Wirtz, W. Willard (1912 -); Lawyer (Box 1, Folder 9, Box 20, Folder 20, Box 22)
- Withrow, Gardner R. (1892 -); Cong., 3rd & 7th Wis. (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Witter, Dean (1887 -); Partner, Dean Witter Co. (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Won, Pat, A. B. () (Box 3, Folder 39)
- WOODSIDE (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Woolner, Sidney H. (1911 -); Govt. official (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Wooten, Ben H. (1894 -); Banker (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Worsley, John C. () (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Wright, James C. Jr. (1922 -); Cong., 12th Tex. (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Wright, W. H. S. () (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Wyman, Parker D. (1922 -); Fgn. serv. officer (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Yamaguchi, Jack (Private bill) (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Yearbooks, agriculture (Box 1, Folder 11, Folder 12)
- Young, Anna Sutter (grandd. of Johann) (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Young, Clifton (1905 -); Artist (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Young, Philip (1916 -); Ambassador (Box 2, Folder 4, Box 7, Folder 3)
- YOUNGER, J. ARTHUR, PERSONAL
  - General file, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Biography, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Christmas cards, 1965 - 1967 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Congratulations (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - 83rd Club (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Gifts, 1955 - 1956 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Lodges, Clubs, etc., 1957 - 1960 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - In House, 1959 - 1960 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Speeches by, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Thanks from, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Memorial addresses book (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - For Congress Comm. (Box 22, Folder 30)
- YOUTH SYMPHONY (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Zimmerman, Edwin M. () (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Zuckert, Eugene M. (1911 -); Lawyer (Box 1, Folder 15)
- MISCELLANEOUS ITEMS (Box BOX 23)
  - News Releases, 1953 - 1954
  - Newsletters, 1965 - 1967; 1953 - 1962
  - Roll call votes records: 1965, - 1964
  - Extra copies of newsletter, 1966 - 1967
Index to J.A.Y.'s Government Record
- From the San Francisco Chronicle, Columns by Arthur Hoppe, January 10, 1963 (Box Box 8,, Folder 8-9, Page Page A 11-12)
- I'm Fed Up To Here Adm. Ben Moreell, January 10, 1963 (Page Page A 13-14)
- The Budgetary Outlook and Its Meaning for Federal Expenditure and Tax Policy Dr. Raymond J. Saulnier, Barnard College, Columbia University, January 10, 1963 (Page Page A 31-34)
- The Current Attitude Toward the Monroe Doctrine and Our Relations With Latin American Commonwealth Club of California, January 10, 1963 (Page Page A 44-45)
- Our Heritage of Boldness Catherine D. Bowen Published in Sports Illustrated, January 10, 1963 (Page Page A56-58)
- Going Now and Paying Later Jenkin Lloyd Jones, January 17, 1963 (Page Page A117)
- Timely Remarks by Art Hoppe of the S. F. Chronicle, January 17, 1963 (Page Page A119-120)
- Monkey Wrench in the Economy David Lawrence, January 28, 1963 (Page Page A 311-312)
- The Political Perils of Foreign Aid William S. White, January 29, 1963 (Page Page A372)
- Firsthand Report of a Recent Trip Around the World Mr. Calvin K. Katter, January 31, 1963 (Page Page A431-432)
- Containerization and Transport Economics Morris Forgash, Pres. United Freight Co., February 4, 1963 (Page Page A506-508)
- The Crisis in U. S. Transportation David Mackie, Chairman Eastern Railroads Presidents Conference, February 4, 1963 (Page Page A519-520)
- The Union is Good-Good and Sick Art Hoppe, San Francisco Chronicle, February 4, 1963 (Page Page)
- The Point of No Return Allison R. Maxwell, Jr., February 5, 1963 (Page Page A530-532)
- U. S. Citizens Imprisoned in Cuba JAY's Comments, February 5, 1963 (Page Page 1742)
- Communist Takeover in the Western Hemisphere JAY's Comments, February 7, 1963 (Page Page 1861)
- Bipartisan Foreign Policy-Cuba JAY's comments, February 25, 1963 (Page Page 2821)
- Art Hoppe's Columns San Francisco Chronicle, February 25, 1963 (Page Page A953)
- Education and Labor Committee Funds Should Be Cut JAY's Remarks re Adam Clayton Powell, February 26, 1963 (Page Page 2863)
- Dialog on the Problems of the National Economy JAY's Remarks, March 4, 1963 (Page Page 3216)
- The British Medical Society Dr. John Callanan, March 4, 1963 (Page Page A1116)
- Free Enterprise-The True Foundation of a Free World JAY's Comments, March 7, 1963 (Page Page 3575)
- Criticism Against Republicans JAY's Remarks, March 11, 1963 (Page Page 3757)
- The Late Clyde Doyle JAY's Comments, March 14, 1963 (Page Page 3909)
- Art Hoppe Writes About National Problems, March 19, 1963 (Page Page A1545)
- Comments on the President's Economic Report Charles E. Walker, Executive Vice-Pres., Am.erican Bankers Assoc., March 19, 1963 (Page Page A1552)
- Germany Shall Be Reunited, but By Negotiation, Plebiscite His Excellency K. Heinrich Knappstein, Ambassador of the Federal Republic of Germany to the United States., March 21, 1963 (Page Page A 1606)
- Art Hoppe's Columns, March 23, 1963 (Page Page A 1772)
- Vote of the Commonwealth Club of California in U. S. Attitude Toward Red China, April 2, 1963 (Page Page A 1909)
- Foreign Aid Won't Improve Lot of Underdeveloped Nations Unless Population Growth Rate Declines Gen. William H. Draper before the Commonwealth Club, April 2, 1963 (Page Page A 1934)
- A Study on Labor Realtions Conducted by the Univ. of Sanat Clara Dr. Lawrence C. Lockley, School of Business, Santa Clara., April 9, 1963 (Page Page A 2150)
- Victory in the Cold War-What It Is, and How Can We Gain It? Honorable Karl R. Bendetsen., April 11, 1963 (Page Page A 2237-2239)
- More Comments By Art Hoppe of the San Francisco Chronicle, April 11, 1963 (Page Page A 2251)
- Refreshing Remarks By Art Hoppe, April 11, 1963 (Page Page A 2244)
- East European Anti-Red Exiles Support Policy Being Reversed Robert S. Allen and Paul Scott, April 11, 1963 (Page Page 6039)
- The Violent Revolutionaries Trinidad Guardian, April 23, 1963 (Page Page A 2385)
- Art Hoppe's Columns, April 23, 1963 (Page Page A 2381)
- The Ugly Communist Mr. Robert A. Stanton, April 23, 1963 (Page Page A 2374)
- Statement By Commission on Cancer on Smoking and and Health California Medical Association, April 24, 1963 (Page Page A 2432)
- Profits and Freedom Mr. R. G. Follis, Chairman of the Board, Standard Oil of California, April 24, 1963 (Page Page A 2473)
- Art Hoppe's Columns, April 25, 1963 (Page Page)
- It Seems To me Howard Harris, April 29, 1963 (Page Page A 586)
- A Plan To Create Jobs in American Industry Through Stimulation of Production and World Markets Dick Elkus, April 29, 1963 (Page Page A 2570)
- J.A.Y.'s Remarks on H.R. 5888, April 30, 1963 (Page Page)
- U.S. Economy and Cold War Competition Commonwealth Club of California, May 6, 1963 (Page Page A 2774)
- The Wilderness Bill Mr. E. R. Stallings, Pres. National Horsemen's Assoc., May 6, 1963 (Page Page A 2760)
- Iden That Soviet System Is Maturing Is Dangerous Illusion Mr. John Davis Lodge, May 8, 1963 (Page Page A 2875)
- We Go To Mexico To Get the Truth About the Bracero Program Jack Pickett and Don Taylor, May 8, 1963 (Page Page A 2883)
- Art Hoppe's Columns, May 9, 1963 (Page Page A 2921)
- Bay of Pigs Survivors Get New Ultimatum on Invasion Robert S. Allen and Paul Scott, May 13, 1963 (Page Page A 2948)
- Art Hoppe's Columns, May 20, 1963 (Page Page A 3151)
- Government Versus Consulting Engineers Report by Consulting Engineers Council, Committee on Private Enterprise, May 23, 1963 (Page Page A 3268)